searchinitiatives.com 2008-10-11

# PrivacyPolicy

•

| 

Search Initiatives has a strong commitment to respecting the privacy of all visitors to our directories and local electronic marketplaces. This policy covers how Search Initiatives treats personal information that it collects and receives, including information related to your past use of Search Initiatives’ services. "Personal information" is information about you and or your business that is personally identifiable such as your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.  
  
•

| 

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Search Initiatives does not own or control, or to people that Search Initiatives does not employ or manage. In particular, Search Initiatives has no control over the privacy policies of any vendor or publisher’s website linked through our directories or local electronic marketplaces.  
  
•

| 

Search Initiatives collects personal information when you register your company with Search Initiatives or when you use a credit card. Search Initiatives may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.  
  
•

| 

When advertisers register their company, we ask for information such as: their name, phone number, email address, zip code, occupation, industry and various industry-based criteria. This information may be made available to the public as a listing in our directory pages, within a coupon ad or text ad. Additionally, this information may be made available to a site visitor to whom you/we send a reply to an inquiry.  
  
•

| 

Search Initiatives automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Search Initiatives’ cookie information, and the page you request.  
  
•

| 

In accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, Search Initiatives does not intend to record personal information submitted by children younger than 13 years old. Children under 13 years old should submit personally identifiable information to Search Initiatives only with the explicit permission of their parent or legal guardian.  
  
•

| 

Search Initiatives will not contact children under age 13 about special offers or for marketing purposes.  
  
•

| 

Search Initiatives does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:  
  
| 

°

| 

We provide the information to trusted (publishers) partners who work on behalf of or with Search Initiatives under confidentiality agreements. These publishers may use your personal information to help Search Initiatives communicate with you about offers from Search Initiatives directory advertisers and our marketing (publishing) partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.  
  
| 

°

| 

We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;  
  
| 

°

| 

We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Search Initiatives” terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.  
  
| 

°

| 

We transfer information about you if Search Initiatives is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Search Initiatives will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.  
  
•

| 

Search Initiatives may set and access Search Initiatives’ cookies on your computer.  
  
•

| 

Search Initiatives may update this policy. We will place a prominent notice on our portion of the publisher’s site about significant changes in the way we treat personal information.
